1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. custom.BrowserHelper.closeFirefoxPopup()
17. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-create-new-account"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Email"), "salahemailgmail.com")
25. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "")
29. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "")
33. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-sign-up"))
37. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Registration/verify-Email"), "Please enter a valid email address")
41. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Registration/verify-required"), "Required")
45. takeScreenshot()
49. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Email"), "agung.priyadi@gtech.digital")
53. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
57. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Las")
61. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-sign-up"))
65. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Registration/verify-length"), "Password length is 6-20 digits")
69. takeScreenshot()
73. closeBrowser()